CURRICULUM VITAE

Dane osobowe

Name/Surname: Damian Wilkołek
Date of birth: 7 marzec 1991r
Phone: 531000605

Email: d.wilkolek@hotmail.com

Key qualifications

Junior Java Developer with more than one year of experience in web application development based on Java. Specialized mainly in backend but also in frontend. Knowledge of Spring, JSP, EJB. Skilled in AJAX and JavaScript. High motivated person focus on professional development, willing to learn new technologies.

Work experience

KAMSOFT S.A.

Dates: 10.2013 – present
Position held: Java Developer

Responsibilities: Working on P1 Project - developing applications for Ministry of Health. Taking care mainly of

backend (70%) but also focused on frontend (30%).

Used technologies: Spring Framework, Spring Web Flow, Spring Web Services, jQuery, AJAX,

Mockito, Unit Tests

Miastostrada

Dates: 01.2013 – 12.2013

Position held: PHP Developer

Responsibilities: Creating and maintaining website on CMS created especially for this website

LGBS Software

Dates: 02.2013 – 06.2013

Position held: PHP/JS Intern

Responsibilities: Working for Sygnity SA - PHP project.

Used technologies: Zend, Json, Dojo, PostgreSQL, JavaScript(jQuery)

IBM Poland

Dates: 10.20132 – 12.2012

Position held: Trainee

Responsibilities: IBM InfoSphere Streams & Performance management and optimization solutions for IBM

DB2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows

Education

Dates: 2010 - 2013

Title: Bachelor of Engineering

University: Silesian University of Technology; Faculty of Materials Engineering and Metallurgy,

Information Technology.

Trainings, conferences and certifications

2013 - Certificate of IBM DB2 Academic Associate: DB2 Database and Application Fundamentals

2012 - Certificate of Internal Auditor information security management system according to ISO 27001

2010 - European Computer Driving License - level expert

Languages

English - Upper-Intermediate

German - Basic

Skills and competences

- More than one year of experience in developing web applications based on Java,
- Specialized mainly in backend but also in frontend,
- Knowledge of software testing technologies: JUnit, Mockito,
- Skilled in JEE software development, especially in technologies: Spring, Hibernate, JSP, EJB,
- Knowledge of frontend technologies such as: AJAX, JavaScript, HTML/CSS,
- Knowledge of Web Services,
- Some experience in XML,
- Experience in relational databases such as: Oracle, MySQL and PostgreSQL,
- Very good knowledge of software tools for software development: Maven, Ant, SVN, JIRA, Eclipse, pgAdmin, SQL Developer, SOAP UI, FireBug,
- Additional knowledge of Kohana, ASP.NET MVC 3,
- Knowledge of programming languages such as: C#, C/C++, Delphi.

I hereby authorize you to process my personal data included in my job application for the needs of the recruitment process (in accordance with the Personnel Protection Act of 29.08.1997 no 133 position 883).